YWCA of the U.S.A. Records. Record Group 6. Program: Series VI. Publications
Sophia Smith Collection
- SERIES VI. PUBLICATIONS
  - Books
    - Wilfrid Rowell Patriotism and the Christian Life, 1918 (Box 674, Folder 5)
    - A. Maude Royden
      - Consider the Days, 1942 (Box 674, Folder 6)
      - Women at the World's Crossroads, 1922 (Box 674, Folder 7)
    - Letty Russell Ferment of Freedom, 1972 (Box 674, Folder 8)
    - Dothory {sic} Sabistan and Margaret Hiller Toward Better Race Relations, 1949 (Box 674, Folder 9)
    - Dorothy Sara Primer for Hostesses, 1950 (Box 674, Folder 10)
    - Mabel Schadt Cafeteria Recipes, 1925 (Box 674, Folder 11)
    - Janie Scott Easy to Make Fashion Accessories, 1953 (Box 674, Folder 12)
    - Roger L. Shinn Beyond This Darkness, 1946 (Box 674, Folder 13)
    - Mary S. Sims and Rhoda E. McCulloch, compilers, Women and Leadership, 1938 (Box 674, Folder 14)
    - Elvira J. Slack A Canticle of the Year, 1920, and Christ in the Poetry of Today (compiled and reassembled from an anthology originated by Martha Foote Crow), 1928 (Box 674, Folder 15)
    - Robert Seneca Smith Fundamentals of Daily Living, 1921, 1922 (Box 674, Folder 16-17)
    - Clarissa Spencer Saints and Ladies, 1925 (Box 674, Folder 18)
    - Dorothy Gladys Spicer
      - The Book of Festivals, 1944, and 1947 (Box 674, Folder 19)
      - Folk Festivals and the Foreign Community, 1923, and From an English Oven, 1948 (Box 674, Folder 20)
      - Holiday Parties, 1939, and Parties for Young Americans, 1940 (Box 675, Folder 1)
      - Windows Open to the World, 1947 (Box 675, Folder 2)
    - B.B.T. Youth Searching: The Spiritual Autobiography of a Modern Girl, 1928 (Box 675, Folder 3)
    - Ordway Tead The Case for Democracy and its Meaning for Modern Life, 1938 (Box 675, Folder 4)
    - Helen Thoburn Christian Citizenship, 1924 (Box 675, Folder 5)
    - Harleigh B. Trecker Group Process in Administration, 1946, and Social Group Work: Principles and Practices, 1948 (Box 675, Folder 6)
    - Grace Trine (compiler) Dreams and Voices, 1920 (Box 675, Folder 7)
    - Ruth Wadsworth Charm By Choice, 1928, 1930, 1939 revised (Box 675, Folder 8-9)
    - Nora Waln The Street of Precious Pearls, 1925 (Box 675, Folder 10)
    - Louis Wasserman Handbook of Political 'Isms,' 1941 (Box 675, Folder 11)
    - Jane Shaw Ward Tajar Tales, 1947 (Box 675, Folder 12)
    - Helen Webster Shower Parties for All Occasions, 1949 (Box 675, Folder 13)
    - Florence Wells, assembler, Tama: The Diary of a Japanese School Girl, 1920 (Box 675, Folder 14)
    - Eleanor Wembridge Let's Understand Each Other: Psychology for People Who Do Not Understand Themselves - or You, 1940 (Box 675, Folder 15)
    - Yolanda Wilkerson Interracial Programs of Student YWCAs, 1948 (Box 675, Folder 16)
    - Elizabeth Wilson
      - The Road Ahead, 1918 (Box 675, Folder 17)
      - Through an Indian Counting Glass, 1926 (Box 675, Folder 18)
    - Winnifred Wygal Reflections of the Spirit, 1948 (Box 675, Folder 19)
    - Agavnie Y. Yeghenian The Red Flag at Ararat, 1932 (Box 675, Folder 20)
  - Serials
    - Bound Preservation copies, [COPIES available IN ALUMNAE GYM PERIODICALS COLLECTION]
      - Association Monthly
        - Feb 1907-Jan 1917 (Box 676)
        - Feb 1917-Aug 1922 (Box 677)
      - Womans Press
        - Sep 1922-Dec 1923 (Box 677)
        - Jan 1924-Dec 1929 (Box 678)
        - Jan 1930-Dec 1936 (Box 679)
        - Jan 1937-Dec 1945 (Box 680)
        - Jan 1946-Dec 1950 (Box 681)
      - YWCA Magazine
        - Jan 1951-Dec 1962 (Box 681)
        - Jan 1963-Dec 1973 (Box 682)
      - National YWCA Bulletin: News From 600, 1951-62 (Box 682)
      - YWCA Interchange, 1974-98 (Box 683, Folder 1-4)
    - Unbound copies [incomplete]
      - Association Monthly
        - Feb 1907-1910 (Box 684, Folder 1-18)
        - 1911-15 (Box 685, Folder 1-16)
        - 1916-Aug 1918 (Box 686, Folder 1-15)
        - Sep 1918-1920 (Box 687, Folder 1-13)
        - 1921-Apr 1922 (Box 688, Folder 1-5)
      - Womans Press
        - Oct 1922-Oct 1923 (Box 688, Folder 6-11)
        - Nov 1923-Jun 1925 (Box 689, Folder 1-10)
        - Jul 1925-Oct 1927 (Box 690, Folder 1-11)
        - Nov 1927-Oct 1929 (Box 691, Folder 1-12)
        - Nov 1929-Mar 1932 (Box 692, Folder 1-10)
        - Apr 1932-Sep 1935 (Box 693, Folder 1-11)
        - Oct 1935-Dec 1937 (Box 694, Folder 1-9)
        - Jan 1938-Jun 1940 (Box 695, Folder 1-10)
        - Jul 1940-Aug 1943 (Box 696, Folder 1-14)
        - Sep 1943-Oct 1946 (Box 697, Folder 1-24)
        - Nov 1946-Dec 1950 (Box 698, Folder 1-16)
      - YWCA Magazine
        - Jan-Dec 1951 (Box 698, Folder 17-19)
        - Jan 1952-May 1968 (Box 699, Folder 1-20)
        - Jun 1968-Dec 1973 (Box 700, Folder 1-8)
      - National YWCA Bulletin: News From 600, 1951-62 (Box 700, Folder 9-19)
      - YWCA Interchange [copy 2], 1974-98 (Box 701, Folder 1-4)